<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-05-10T00:38:07.336Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.5.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Food in Hilo, Hawaii]]></title>
        <id>http://tynan.com/hilo</id>
        <link href="http://tynan.com/hilo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T20:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't really consider myself to be a foodie, but the food in Hilo is SO good that it's one of the things I most look forward to every time I visit. I've been to the major Hawaiian islands and have had great food on all of them, but Hilo is definitely in a league of it']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I try not to make unlikable software (and features)]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/08/Try-not-to-make-unlikable-software.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/08/Try-not-to-make-unlikable-software.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am writing to you from The Sky. On my flight today, I noticed an example of
&ldquo;unlikable&rdquo; software — something I&rsquo;ve been increasingly aware of recently
— inspiring me to pull out my laptop and write. On this plane, there are
displays in the back of each seat which provides entertainment for the person
seated one row back. Newer planes no longer include these, given that in
$CURRENTYEAR everyone would just prefer some power for their phone or laptop.
Nevertheless, you can still end up a pla…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[godocs.io six months later]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/07/godocs.io-six-months-later.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/07/godocs.io-six-months-later.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We&rsquo;re six months on from forking godoc.org following its upstream
deprecation, and we&rsquo;ve made a lot of great improvements since. For those
unaware, the original godoc.org was replaced with pkg.go.dev, and a redirect was
set up. The new website isn&rsquo;t right for many projects — one of the most
glaring issues is the narrow list of software licenses pkg.go.dev will display
documentation for. To continue serving the needs of projects which preferred the
old website, we forked the project and set…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attainable Excellence]]></title>
        <id>http://tynan.com/excellence</id>
        <link href="http://tynan.com/excellence"/>
        <updated>2021-05-02T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By strange coincidence, I know a lot of people starting restaurants. Some are friends, some are family members, and some I've just gotten to know because I eat at their restaurants all the time. One is a world class chocolate company, another is a pizza place, another is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan | Life Outside the Box</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency is an abject disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/26/Cryptocurrency-is-a-disaster.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/26/Cryptocurrency-is-a-disaster.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is long overdue. Let&rsquo;s get it over with.
Hey! If you write a comment about this article online,
  disclose your stake in cryptocurrency. I will explain why later in this post.
  For my part, I held &lt;$10,000 USD worth of Bitcoin prior to 2016, plus small
  amounts of altcoins. I made a modest profit on my holdings. Today my stake in
  all cryptocurrency is $0.

Starting on May 1st, users of sourcehut&rsquo;s CI service will be required to be on a
paid account, a change which will affect ab…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filter More Out]]></title>
        <id>http://tynan.com/filter</id>
        <link href="http://tynan.com/filter"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T20:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're all looking for the next thing that we should be doing or paying attention to. Maybe that's even part of why you read this blog. This is a good pursuit of course, but it often seems to me that people don't spend enough time figuring out what they shouldn't be payin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan | Life Outside the Box</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recommended read: Why Lichess will always be free]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/23/Lichess.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/23/Lichess.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Signal-boosting this excellent article from Lichess: Why Lichess will always be free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parsers all the way down: writing a self-hosting parser]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/22/Our-self-hosted-parser-design.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/22/Our-self-hosted-parser-design.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the things we&rsquo;re working on in my new programming language is a
self-hosting compiler. Having a self-hosted compiler is a critical step in the
development of (some) programming languages: it signals that the language is
mature enough to be comfortably used to implement itself. While this isn&rsquo;t right
for some languages (e.g. shell scripts), for a systems programming language like
ours, this is a crucial step in our bootstrapping plan. Our self-hosted parser
design was completed this week, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Self Educating Child]]></title>
        <id>https://www.mrmoneymustache.com/2021/04/18/the-self-educating-child/</id>
        <link href="https://www.mrmoneymustache.com/2021/04/18/the-self-educating-child/"/>
        <updated>2021-04-18T21:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So it looks like my 15-year-old is officially a high-school dropout. Halfway through ninth grade, emboldened perhaps by the taste of freedom that Covid-era remote learning had provided, he realized that the whole system was just too slow and inefficient for him, and was &#8220;Getting in the way of his work.&#8221; So as it looks [&#8230;]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mr. Money Mustache</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Invest in Friendships]]></title>
        <id>http://tynan.com/friendvestments</id>
        <link href="http://tynan.com/friendvestments"/>
        <updated>2021-04-18T16:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In just about any way I can think of, I have an amazing life. But of all of the aspects of my life that bring me happiness, the most important one is the relationships I have with my friends and family. This is probably true for almost everyone, but it's odd to me how mo]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan | Life Outside the Box</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Status update, April 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/15/Status-update-April-2021.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/15/Status-update-April-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another month goes by! I&rsquo;m afraid that I have very little to share this month.
You can check out the sourcehut &ldquo;what&rsquo;s cooking&rdquo; post for sourcehut news,
but outside of that I have focused almost entirely on the programming language
project this month, for which the details are kept private.
The post calling for contributors led to a lot of answers and we&rsquo;ve brought
several new people on board — thanks for answering the call! I&rsquo;d like to
narrow the range of problems we sti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Developer Certificate of Origin is a great alternative to a CLA]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/12/DCO.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/04/12/DCO.html"/>
        <updated>2021-04-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today Amazon released their fork of ElasticSearch, OpenSearch, and I want
to take a moment to draw your attention to one good decision in particular: its
use of the Developer Certificate of Origin (or &ldquo;DCO&rdquo;).
Previously:
ElasticSearch does not belong to Elastic
Open source means surrendering your monopoly over commercial exploitation
Don&rsquo;t sign a CLA
Elastic betrayed its community when they changed to a proprietary license.  We
could have seen it coming because of a particular trait of the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>