<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-07T01:05:19.567Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build your project in our new language]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/30/Come-build-your-project.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/30/Come-build-your-project.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have a new systems programming project on your todo list? If you’re
feeling adventurous, I would like you to give it a crack in our new systems
programming language, and to use it to drive improvements in the less-developed
areas of our standard library.
Are you making a new coreutils implementation? A little OS kernel? A new shell?
A GUI toolkit? Database system? Web server? Whatever your systems programming
use-case, we think that our language is likely to be a good fit for you, and
your help in proving that, and spurring development to rise to meet your needs,
would be quite welcome.
Here’s our pitch:
XXXX is a systems programming language designed to be simple and robust. XXXX
uses a static type system, manual memory management, and a minimal runtime.
It is well-suited to writing operating systems, system tools, compilers,
networking software, and other low-level, high performance tasks.
You can get a peek at how it feels by reading about the finger server I wrote
with it.
Sounds interesting? Please tell me about your project idea!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using io_uring to make a high-performance... finger server]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/24/io_uring-finger-server.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/24/io_uring-finger-server.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m working on adding a wrapper for the Linux io_uring interface to my
secret programming language project. To help learn more about io_uring and
to test out the interface I was designing, I needed a small project whose design
was well-suited for the value-add of io_uring. The Finger protocol is
perfect for this! After being designed in the 70’s and then completely forgotten
about for 50 years, it’s the perfect small and simple network protocol to test
drive this new interface with.
In short, finger will reach out to a remote server and ask for information about
a user. It was used back in the day to find contact details like the user’s
phone number, office address, email address, sometimes their favorite piece of
ASCII art, and, later, a summary of the things they were working on at the
m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Have More Options When You're Weird]]></title>
        <id>http://tynan.com/you-have-more-options-when-youre-weird</id>
        <link href="http://tynan.com/you-have-more-options-when-youre-weird"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T17:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many ways my life is very weird. Sometimes when I'm about to make a statement like that I try to think of a relatable example of how I'm not weird in some way, but it's hard to come up with one. I wear clothes like everyone else... except I only have one set. I sleep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to write release notes]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/19/How-to-write-release-notes.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/19/How-to-write-release-notes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Release notes are a concept most of us are familiar with. When a new software
release is prepared, the release notes tell you what changed, so you understand
what you can expect and how to prepare for the update. They are also
occasionally used to facilitate conversations:

Many of the people tasked with writing release notes have never found themselves
on that side of the screen before. If that describes you, I would like to offer
some advice on how to nail it. Note that this mostly applies to free and ope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[aerc, mbsync, and postfix for maximum comfy offline email]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/17/aerc-with-mbsync-postfix.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/17/aerc-with-mbsync-postfix.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am the original author of the aerc mail client, though my official
relationship with it today is marginal at best. I think that, with hindsight,
I’ve come to understand that the “always online” approach of aerc’s IMAP
implementation is less than ideal. The next email client (which will exist at
some point!) will improve on this design, but, since it’s still my favorite
email client despite these flaws, they will have to be worked around.
To this end, I have updated my personal aerc setup to take advantage…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Status update, May 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/16/Status-update-May-2021.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/16/Status-update-May-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! This update is a bit late. I was travelling all day yesterday without
internet, so I could not prepare these. After my sister and I got vaccinated, I
took a trip to visit her at her home in beautiful Hawaii — it felt great
after a year of being trapped within these same four walls. I hope you get that
vaccine and things start to improve for you, too!
In SourceHut news, I’ve completed and shipped the first version of the
builds.sr.ht GraphQL API. Another update, implementing the write functionality,
w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pinebook Pro review]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/14/Pinebook-Pro-review.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/14/Pinebook-Pro-review.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I received the original Pinebook for free from the good folks at Pine64 a few
years ago, when I visited Berlin to work with the KDE developers. Honestly, I
was underwhelmed. The performance was abysmal and ARM is a nightmare to work
with. For these reasons, I was skeptical when I bought the Pinebook Pro. I have
also spoken of my disdain for modern laptops in general before: the state
of laptops in $CURRENTYEAR is abysmal. As such, I have been using a ThinkPad
X200, an 11 year old laptop, as my sole laptop f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Make Purchasing Decisions]]></title>
        <id>http://tynan.com/buying</id>
        <link href="http://tynan.com/buying"/>
        <updated>2021-05-13T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite being a pretty severe minimalist for a long time, I think I'm now known a lot for what I buy. I worry about this a little bit sometimes, because I don't think being a great consumer is very meaningful. On the other hand, buying the right things is a good substitu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Best Food in Hilo, Hawaii]]></title>
        <id>http://tynan.com/hilo</id>
        <link href="http://tynan.com/hilo"/>
        <updated>2021-05-08T20:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I don't really consider myself to be a foodie, but the food in Hilo is SO good that it's one of the things I most look forward to every time I visit. I've been to the major Hawaiian islands and have had great food on all of them, but Hilo is definitely in a league of it']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>