<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-15T00:40:00.210Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Provided "as is", without warranty of any kind]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/14/Provided-as-is-without-warranty.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/14/Provided-as-is-without-warranty.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MIT license contains the following text, in all uppercase no less:
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.
The BSD licenses, GPL family of licenses, Apache 2.0, Mozilla Public License,
and likely any other license you’d care to name, have similar clauses of their
own. It’s worth taking a moment to consider the implications of this statement
and what it says about the social aspects of free and open source software.
Many people who rely on free and open source software feel entitled to some
degree of workitude or support from the developers, or think that the developers
have a responsibility to provide good maintenance, or any …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Switched Back to WordPress and What I Learned]]></title>
        <id>https://tynan.com/?p=3502</id>
        <link href="https://tynan.com/wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T20:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you read the blog through the web you may notice that, for the first time in about a decade, it looks different. If you get posts by email you hopefully don’t notice anything, but since it’s a whole new system… who knows. A little over nine years ago, my good friend Todd and I… Continue reading Why I Switched Back to WordPress and What I Learned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I will be moving to the Netherlands]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/07/The-Netherlands.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/07/The-Netherlands.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had been planning a move to the Netherlands for a while, at least until a
large COVID-shaped wrench was thrown into the gears. However, I was fully
vaccinated by early April, and there are signs of the border opening up now, so
my plans have been slowly getting back on track. I sent off my visa application
today, and assuming I can navigate the pandemic-modified procedures, I should be
able to make my move fairly soon. It’s a little bit intimidating, but I am
looking forward to it!
Quick note: I am looking for temporary housing in NL; somewhere I can stay for
6-12 months with a permanent mailing address for receiving immigration-related
documents. I would prefer to rent out a room than to use some kind of commercial
accommodation, to be certain that I can receive mail from the immigratio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Maximum Enjoyment From Cruises]]></title>
        <id>https://tynan.com/?p=3488</id>
        <link href="https://tynan.com/how-to-get-maximum-enjoyment-from-cruises/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-06T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that I absolutely love cruising. Every year I organize a few cruises and try to get as many of my friends as possible to join me. The only limit I have on how many days per year I spend at sea is how many days I can convince friends to cruise with… Continue reading How to Get Maximum Enjoyment From Cruises]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build your project in our new language]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/30/Come-build-your-project.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/30/Come-build-your-project.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you have a new systems programming project on your todo list? If you’re
feeling adventurous, I would like you to give it a crack in our new systems
programming language, and to use it to drive improvements in the less-developed
areas of our standard library.
Are you making a new coreutils implementation? A little OS kernel? A new shell?
A GUI toolkit? Database system? Web server? Whatever your systems programming
use-case, we think that our language is likely to be a good fit for you, and
your help in proving that, and spurring development to rise to meet your needs,
would be quite welcome.
Here’s our pitch:
XXXX is a systems programming language designed to be simple and robust. XXXX
uses a static type system, manual memory management, and a minimal runtime.
It is well-suited to writing operating systems, system tools, compilers,
networking software, and other low-level, high performance tasks.
You can get a peek at how it feels by reading about the finger server I wrote
with it.
Sounds interesting? Please tell me about your project idea!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Variance and Investing]]></title>
        <id>https://tynan.com/variance/</id>
        <link href="https://tynan.com/variance/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T11:20:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the best things to come from my career as a professional gambler is a deep unconscious understanding of risk, odds, EV, and variance. The downside to this is that I see people make fundamental errors all the time, especially in investing, and it really bothers me. Usually I notice these errors not because… Continue reading Variance and Investing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using io_uring to make a high-performance... finger server]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/24/io_uring-finger-server.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/24/io_uring-finger-server.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m working on adding a wrapper for the Linux io_uring interface to my
secret programming language project. To help learn more about io_uring and
to test out the interface I was designing, I needed a small project whose design
was well-suited for the value-add of io_uring. The Finger protocol is
perfect for this! After being designed in the 70’s and then completely forgotten
about for 50 years, it’s the perfect small and simple network protocol to test
drive this new interface with.
In short, finger will reach out to a remote server and ask for information about
a user. It was used back in the day to find contact details like the user’s
phone number, office address, email address, sometimes their favorite piece of
ASCII art, and, later, a summary of the things they were working on at the
m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Have More Options When You're Weird]]></title>
        <id>http://tynan.com/you-have-more-options-when-youre-weird</id>
        <link href="http://tynan.com/you-have-more-options-when-youre-weird"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T17:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many ways my life is very weird. Sometimes when I'm about to make a statement like that I try to think of a relatable example of how I'm not weird in some way, but it's hard to come up with one. I wear clothes like everyone else... except I only have one set. I sleep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Have More Options When You’re Weird]]></title>
        <id>https://tynan.com/you-have-more-options-when-youre-weird/</id>
        <link href="https://tynan.com/you-have-more-options-when-youre-weird/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T10:24:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many ways my life is very weird. Sometimes when I’m about to make a statement like that I try to think of a relatable example of how I’m not weird in some way, but it’s hard to come up with one. I wear clothes like everyone else… except I only have one set. I… Continue reading You Have More Options When You’re Weird]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to write release notes]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/19/How-to-write-release-notes.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/19/How-to-write-release-notes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Release notes are a concept most of us are familiar with. When a new software
release is prepared, the release notes tell you what changed, so you understand
what you can expect and how to prepare for the update. They are also
occasionally used to facilitate conversations:

Many of the people tasked with writing release notes have never found themselves
on that side of the screen before. If that describes you, I would like to offer
some advice on how to nail it. Note that this mostly applies to free and ope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[aerc, mbsync, and postfix for maximum comfy offline email]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/17/aerc-with-mbsync-postfix.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/05/17/aerc-with-mbsync-postfix.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am the original author of the aerc mail client, though my official
relationship with it today is marginal at best. I think that, with hindsight,
I’ve come to understand that the “always online” approach of aerc’s IMAP
implementation is less than ideal. The next email client (which will exist at
some point!) will improve on this design, but, since it’s still my favorite
email client despite these flaws, they will have to be worked around.
To this end, I have updated my personal aerc setup to take advantage…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>