<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/index.html</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-30T00:43:38.096Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://cyrusmg.github.io/rss-reader/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://tynan.com/?p=3544</id>
        <link href="https://tynan.com/automatichome/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T21:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the projects I’ve been tinkering with constantly for the past nine months or so that we’ve lived at our new house is home automation. I’ve been into home automation since about 1996 and have had a fully automated house ever since 2003 or so. Even my RV was so automated that it unlocked… Continue reading Home Automation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You can't capture the nuance of my form fields]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/27/You-cant-capture-the-nuance.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/27/You-cant-capture-the-nuance.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check out this text box:
Consectetur qui consequatur voluptatibus voluptatem sit sint perspiciatis. Eos aspernatur ad laboriosam quam numquam quo. Quia reiciendis illo quo praesentium. Dolor porro et et sit dolorem quisquam totam quae.
Ea molestias a aspernatur dignissimos suscipit incidunt. Voluptates in vel qui quaerat. Asperiores vel sit rerum est ipsam. Odio aut aut voluptate qui voluptatem.
Quia consequatur provident fugiat voluptatibus consequatur. Est sunt aspernatur velit. Officiis a dolorum accusantium. Sint est ut inventore.
Here are some of the nuances of using this text box on my operating system
(Linux) and web browser (Firefox):
Double clicking selects a word, and triple-clicking selects the whole line. If
I double- or triple-click-and-hold, I can drag the mouse to expand the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A finger client]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/24/finger-client.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/24/finger-client.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a short follow-up to the io_uring finger server article posted
about a month ago. In the time since, we have expanded our language with a more
complete networking stack, most importantly by adding a DNS resolver. I have
used these improvements to write a small client implementation of the finger
protocol.
use fmt;
use io;
use net::dial;
use os;
use strings;

@init fn registersvc() void = dial::registersvc("tcp", "finger", [], 79);
@noreturn fn usage() void = fmt::fatal("Usage: {} <user>[@<host>]", os::args[0]);

export fn main() void = {
	if (len(os::args) != 2) usage();

	const items = strings::split(os::args[1], "@");
	defer free(items);
	if (len(items) == 0) usage();

	const user = items[0];
	const host = if (len(items) == 1) "localhost"
		else if (len(items) == 2) items[1]
		el…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superhuman 4.5 in August]]></title>
        <id>https://tynan.com/?p=3539</id>
        <link href="https://tynan.com/superhuman-4-5-in-august/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T18:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My live event, Superhuman 4.5, will be held in Las Vegas on August 14th and 15th (with an optional meetup the night before). Reflecting on the changes brought about by the pandemic, one of the things I missed most was doing these Superhuman events. They’re a ton of fun and very gratifying for me to… Continue reading Superhuman 4.5 in August]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Status update, June 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/15/Status-update-June-2021.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/15/Status-update-June-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hiya! Got another status update for you. First, let me share this picture that
my dad and I took on our recent astronomy trip (click for full res):

Bonus Venus:

So, what’s new? With SourceHut, there are a few neat goings-on. For one, thanks
to Michael Forney putting the finishing touches on the patchset, the
long-awaited NetBSD image is now available for builds.sr.ht. Also, the initial
lists.sr.ht GraphQL API design is in place, and Simon Ser is working on a new
and improved implementation of email discussion parsing for us to use. I’ve also
redesigned the registration & onboarding flow based on a maintainer/contributor
distinction, which should help people understand how sourcehut works a bit
better. Also, as promised, the writable GraphQL API for builds.sr.ht is now
available.
I had been working on a new feature for the secret programming language, but in
the course of implementing it, it became clear to me that we need to take a step
back and do some deep refactoring in the compiler. This will probably occupy us
for a couple of months. Even so, some improvements in the standard library have
been made and shall continue to be made. You may have seen a few weeks ago that
I wrote a finger server in the new language, and there’s a bunch of code
for you to read there if you’re interested in learning more.
I also spent some time this month on Simon’s gamja and soju projects.
Libera.chat is running an experimental instance of gamja for their webchat,
and I’ve helped Simon incorporate some of their feedback and apply a layer of
polish to the client. I’m also working on generalizing soju a bit so that we can
eventually utilize it to offer a hosted IRC bouncer for sr.ht users.
That’s all I have to share for now. My foci have been on sourcehut and the
secret language, and will continue to be those. I plan on advancing the work on
the GraphQL APIs for sr.ht and ideally shipping an initial version of the
lists.sr.ht API in a few weeks. I’ll share more news about the new language when
it’s ready. Until next time!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Provided "as is", without warranty of any kind]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/14/Provided-as-is-without-warranty.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/14/Provided-as-is-without-warranty.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MIT license contains the following text, in all uppercase no less:
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.
The BSD licenses, GPL family of licenses, Apache 2.0, Mozilla Public License,
and likely any other license you’d care to name, have similar clauses of their
own. It’s worth taking a moment to consider the implications of this statement
and what it says about the social aspects of free and open source software.
Many people who rely on free and open source software feel entitled to some
degree of workitude or support from the developers, or think that the developers
have a responsibility to provide good maintenance, or any …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I Switched Back to WordPress and What I Learned]]></title>
        <id>https://tynan.com/?p=3502</id>
        <link href="https://tynan.com/wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T20:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you read the blog through the web you may notice that, for the first time in about a decade, it looks different. If you get posts by email you hopefully don’t notice anything, but since it’s a whole new system… who knows. A little over nine years ago, my good friend Todd and I… Continue reading Why I Switched Back to WordPress and What I Learned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I will be moving to the Netherlands]]></title>
        <id>https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/07/The-Netherlands.html</id>
        <link href="https://drewdevault.com/2021/06/07/The-Netherlands.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I had been planning a move to the Netherlands for a while, at least until a
large COVID-shaped wrench was thrown into the gears. However, I was fully
vaccinated by early April, and there are signs of the border opening up now, so
my plans have been slowly getting back on track. I sent off my visa application
today, and assuming I can navigate the pandemic-modified procedures, I should be
able to make my move fairly soon. It’s a little bit intimidating, but I am
looking forward to it!
Quick note: I am looking for temporary housing in NL; somewhere I can stay for
6-12 months with a permanent mailing address for receiving immigration-related
documents. I would prefer to rent out a room than to use some kind of commercial
accommodation, to be certain that I can receive mail from the immigratio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Drew DeVault's blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Maximum Enjoyment From Cruises]]></title>
        <id>https://tynan.com/?p=3488</id>
        <link href="https://tynan.com/how-to-get-maximum-enjoyment-from-cruises/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-06T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s no secret that I absolutely love cruising. Every year I organize a few cruises and try to get as many of my friends as possible to join me. The only limit I have on how many days per year I spend at sea is how many days I can convince friends to cruise with… Continue reading How to Get Maximum Enjoyment From Cruises]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>tynan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>